electrictobacconist.com 2019-02-05

# Electric Tobacconist® USA Cookies & Privacy Policy

**Electric Tobacconist® Cookies Policy**

 **About Cookies**

This website uses cookies. By using this website and agreeing to this policy, you consent to The Electric Tobacconist's use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.

Cookies are files sent by web servers to web browsers and stored by the web browsers.

The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables a web server to identify and track web browsers.

There are two main kinds of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies are deleted from your computer when you close your browser, whereas persistent cookies remain stored on your computer until deleted or until they reach their expiry date.

 **Cookies on Our Website**

The Electric Tobacconist uses the following cookies on this website, for the following purposes:

  *  to improve the website's usability
  *  to administer this website

 **Google Cookies**

The Electric Tobacconist uses Google Analytics to analyze the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store and use this information. Google's privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.

The Electric Tobacconist publishes Google Adsense interest-based advertisements on this website. These are tailored by Google to reflect your interests. To determine your interests, Google will track your behavior across the web using cookies. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser using Google's Ads Preference Manager, available at: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/.  You can opt-out of the Adsense partner network cookie at: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. However, this opt-out mechanism uses a cookie, and if you clear the cookies from your browser, your opt-out will not be maintained. To ensure that an opt-out is maintained in respect of a particular browser, you should use the Google browser plug-in available at: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/plugin.

 **Refusing Cookies**

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. 

In Internet Explorer, you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector. 

In Firefox, you can adjust your cookies settings by clicking “Tools”, “Options” and “Privacy.”

Blocking cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of some websites.

 **Credit**

This document was created using a Contractology template available at [http://www.freenetlaw.com](http://www.freenetlaw.com/).

 **PRIVACY POLICY for www.electrictobacconist.com**

At The Electric Tobacconist, LLC, we are committed to safeguarding and preserving the privacy of our visitors.  
This Privacy Policy explains what happens to any personal data that you provide to us or that we collect from you whilst you visit our site.  
We do update this Policy from time to time so please do review this Policy regularly.  
Information We Collect  
In running and maintaining our website, we may collect and process the following data about you:  
Information about your use of our site, including details of your visits, such as pages viewed and the resources that you access. Such information includes traffic data, location data and other communication data.  
Information provided voluntarily by you. For example, when you register for information or make a purchase.  
Information that you provide when you communicate with us by any means.  
Use of Cookies  
Cookies provide information regarding the computer used by a visitor. We may use cookies where appropriate to gather information about your computer in order to assist us in improving our website.  
We may gather information about your general internet use by using the cookie. Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer and stored on the computer's hard drive. Such information will not identify you personally. It is statistical data. This statistical data does not identify any personal details whatsoever.  
You can adjust the settings on your computer to decline any cookies if you wish. This can easily be done by activating the reject cookies setting on your computer.  
Our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control. Such cookies (if used) would be downloaded once you click on advertisements on our website.  
Use of Your Information  
We use the information that we collect from you to provide our services to you. In addition to this, we may use the information for one or more of the following purposes:  
To provide information to you that you request from us relating to our products or services.  
To provide information to you relating to other products that may be of interest to you. Such additional information will only be provided where you have consented to receive such information.  
To inform you of any changes to our website, services or goods and products.  
If you have previously purchased goods or services from us, we may provide to you details of similar goods or services, or other goods and services, that you may be interested in.  
Where your consent has been provided in advance, we may allow selected third parties to use your data to enable them to provide you with information regarding unrelated goods and services which we believe may interest you. Where such consent has been provided, it can be withdrawn by you at any time.  
Storing Your Personal Data  
In operating our website, it may become necessary to transfer data that we collect from you to locations outside of the European Union for processing and storing. By providing your personal data to us, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We do our upmost to ensure that all reasonable steps are taken to make sure that your data is treated stored securely.  
Unfortunately the sending of information via the internet is not totally secure and on occasion such information can be intercepted. We cannot guarantee the security of data that you choose to send us electronically. Sending such information is entirely at your own risk.  
Disclosing Your Information  
We will not disclose your personal information to any other party other than in accordance with this Privacy Policy and in the circumstances detailed below:  
In the event that we sell any or all of our business to the buyer.  
Where we are legally required by law to disclose your personal information.  
To further fraud protection and reduce the risk of fraud.  
Third Party Links  
On occasion we include links to third parties on this website. Where we provide a link, it does not mean that we endorse or approve that site's policy towards visitor privacy. You should review their privacy policy before sending them any personal data.  
Access to Information  
In accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998, you have the right to access any information that we hold relating to you. Please note that we reserve the right to charge a fee of $10 to cover costs incurred by us in providing you with the information.  
Contacting Us  
Please do not hesitate to contact us regarding any matter relating to this Privacy Policy at hello@electrictobacconist.com.
